Emma LaBelle

< front end web developer >

emlabelle@gmail.com 781-330-5500 www.emmalabelle.com

Driven, self-taught front end developer looking for a junior position with an excellent organization. Strong attention to detail and excellent communication skills honed over 5+ years working in team settings. I am a self-starter and capable problem solver always looking to develop my skills.

Work Experience

MumbleStore

Co-owner, 2015 - 2018

Ran a successful Ebay store as a Top Rated Seller, clearing up to \$4,300 a month in gross sales. Sourced inventory from local yard sales and thrift shops. Packed and shipped out up to 200 orders a month.

CBS Television Studios, Los Angeles

Executive Assistant, 2013 - 2015

Provided administrative support to Vice President of Business Affairs. Drafted, edited and proofread legal agreements and deal memos for above-the-line talent for primetime CBS shows. Coordinated with talent agents and attorneys to ensure timely receipt of executed contracts. Maintained and updated CBS Television Studios database responsible for company-wide agreement tracking.

Interloper Films, Los Angeles

Production Coordinator, 2013

Coordinated the videography and post-production of interviews for seven ongoing docu-series at ATotalDisruption.com. Spearheaded a one-month crowdfunding campaign that raised \$144,000 for continued production of the series. Created budgets, produced and distributed invoices, and kept post-production spreadsheets up to date.

Previous Experience

New York Office, Los Angeles

Executive Assistant, 2010 - 2012

Landscape Entertainment, Los Angeles

2nd Assistant, 2010

Education & Certifications

Free Code Camp

Certifications in Front End, JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Emerson College, Boston

Bachelor's Degree in Writing, Literature and Publishing

Skills

Technical: React, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git, Parcel

Software: Visual Studio Code, Adobe Creative Suite, Google Apps, Microsoft Office Suite

> View my online portfolio at emmalabelle.com and github.com/emlabelle